Alternative data could be generated by scraping social media profiles of companies,
我们可以通过搜集公司的社交媒体资料
tracking building permits or hospital purchases,
跟踪建筑执照或医院设备购买行为
and analyzing satellite imagery to name a few examples.
以及分析卫星图像等创建另类数据
Construction companies file permit requests with
在安装配套设施
local governments when installing components of
和升级设施时
a house and also when upgrading components.
建筑公司会向当地政府申请许可证
This information could be tracked to better understand the housing market.
我们可以跟踪这些信息来更好地了解房地产市场
Some hospitals provide information about purchases of medical equipment and supplies.
某些医院会公布医疗设备和用具的购买信息
This could also be used to assess the sales of
我们还可以利用这些信息
companies that supply medical equipment to these hospitals.
评估向这些医院提供医疗设备的公司的销量
These days, companies have public profiles in major social media platforms.
如今 很多公司在大型社交媒体平台上创建了公开的资料
Information about their employee count, job postings,
信息包括员工人数 招聘信息
employee ratings of the company,
员工对公司的评分
store locations, number of social media followers,
商店位置 社交媒体粉丝数量
number of active users of their mobile apps,
移动应用的活跃用户数
number of check-ins by customers,
客户签到数 等等
and so on, these can be tracked over time to gain insights into a company.
我们可以一直跟踪这些信息 从而了解公司状况
An interesting hypothesis is that companies,
有一个有趣的假设
which are struggling with reduced sales,
即销量不佳的公司
may be more likely to increase marketing on social media.
更有可能在社交媒体上加大营销活动
So, it's possible to look for
所以可以将
recent increased marketing efforts as a potential alpha factor.
最近增加的营销活动看做潜在的 alpha 因子
Satellite images can also be used to get a high level overview of parking lots,
还可以根据卫星图像大致了解停车场
mining sites, oil rigs,
矿区 石油钻塔
shipping ports, and construction zones.
装货港和施工区
A retailer's customer base can be estimated
我们可以通过计算
from counting how many cars visit their retail stores.
进入零售店的车辆数量估算零售商的客户群
Empty parking lots likely suggest fewer customers,
停车场很空表明客户更少
full parking lots suggest more customers and potentially more sales as well.
停车场很满表明有更多客户 销量可能更高
In fact, the parking lot data generated by a startup, Orbital Insight,
实际上 初创公司 Orbital Insight 创建的停车场数据
closely tracked the downward trend of JC Penney's stock price from 2012 to 2017.
紧密跟踪了 JC Penney 股价从 2012 年到 2017 年的下跌走势
Crude oil storage can be tracked by analyzing satellite and drone images.
可以通过分析卫星和无人机图像跟踪原油库
Now, you may be wondering why oil storage is relevant if you're trading equities.
你可能会疑问 为何油库与股票交易有关
Well, crude oil storage is tracked closely
紧密跟踪原油库
in order for oil traders to set prices on a barrel of oil.
可以使石油贸易商对一桶油设定价格
Storage of commodities in general gives an indication of
商品仓储通常可以表示
how much is being produced relative to how much is being consumed.
生产量和消费量是多少
Prices are based on both supply and demand.
价格与供需有关
Storage levels and changes in
存储量和存储量变化
storage levels provide a signal about both supply and demand,
可以表示供需情况
and therefore a signal about the price.
进而提供了价格信号
Price changes of oil trickles down to impact
石油价格变化会逐层影响到
the operation costs of any businesses that rely on petroleum,
依赖于石油 喷气燃料
jet fuel, gasoline, diesel,
汽油 柴油 取暖油
heating oil, and other products that are derived from crude oil.
和由原油制造的其他产品的任何公司的运营成本
These include airlines, trucking,
这些公司包括航空 货运
shipping, and utility companies to name a few.
运输和公用事业公司等
In the US, oil traders closely monitor
在美国 石油交易者
the weekly oil and natural gas storage reports issued
会紧密关注能源信息管理局 (EIA)
by the Energy Information Administration or EIA.
发布的每周石油和天然气存储报告
The EIA surveys crude oil stockholders,
EIA 对原油股东展开问卷调查
which may use floating roof tanks,
他们可能会使用浮顶油罐
fixed roof tanks, underground caverns,
拱顶油罐 地下洞穴
trains, trucks, and pipelines to store crude oil.
火车 卡车和存储原油的管道
Some companies have also looked into tracking oil pipeline
某些公司还会观察油管流量
flows in order to estimate changes in crude oil storage levels.
并据此估算原油存储量的变化
With aerial footage, it's possible to track floating roof tank storage levels.
通过航拍可以跟踪浮顶油罐的存储量
Floating roof tanks are cylinders with a roof that floats on top of the stored oil.
浮顶油罐是指顶盖漂浮在石油上面的油罐
Computer imaging can track shadows to estimate the height of these roofs and
计算机映像可以跟踪阴影并估算这些顶盖的高度
subsequently estimate the volume of crude oil stored in a floating roof tank.
进而估算这些浮顶油罐的原油储量
Orbital Insight produces energy storage estimates based on
Orbital Insight 通过分析美国、OPEC 和中国的
his analysis of this image data for the US, OPEC, and China.
这些影像数据得出了能源存储估值